Guide to the Franklin Bowditch Dexter Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Files on Alumni, Circa 1701-1912; Series I; 9' (22 boxes)
  - Southmayd, Charles Goodrich. 1856 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Southmayd, William. 1761 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Southworth, Edward. 1879 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Southworth, Gideon. 1727 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Southworth, Mase Shepard. 1868 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spalding, Asa Leffingwell. 1832m (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spalding, Josiah. 1813 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spanier, Emil. 1855 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Sparrow, Orson Cowles. 1854 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spayd, Joseph Heister. 1824 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spelman, Robert. 1785 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spencer, Elihu. 1805 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spencer, George Gilman. 1834 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spencer, George Jarvis. 1890p (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spencer, Horatio Nelson. 1821
  - Spencer, Israel Selden. 1857
  - Spencer, James Madison. 1851 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Spencer, Joseph Austin. 1837 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Sprague, William Buell. 1815 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Spring, Andrew Jackson. 1855 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Spring, Samuel. 1821 non-graduate (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Spruill, George Evans. 1814 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Squires, Walter. 1878 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Stafford, Ward. 1812
  - Stanley, George Washington. 1793
    See: Stanley, Oliver, box 16, folder 190.
  - Stanley, Henry. 1801 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Stanley, Nathaniel. 1726 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Stanley, Oliver. 1768 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Stanly, John Wright. 1826 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - Stansbury, Joseph. 1821 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Stanton, Alexander Hamilton. 1859 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Staples, Job. 1808
  - Staples, Seth Perkins. 1797
    See: Smith, Richard (1797), box 16, folder 187.
    See: Wales, John, box 18, folder 211.
  - Staples, Sophos. 1809
  - Stark, James Landon. 1814 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Stark, Nathan. 1811 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Starkey, Stephen William. 1820
    See: Pratt, Howard Eben, box 14, folder 162.
  - Starkweather, Ephraim. 1755 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Starkweather, John. 1825 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Stearns, Elisha. 1796 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Stebbins, Daniel. 1788 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Stebbins, Heman. 1814 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Stebbins, Stephan Williams. 1781 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Stedman, Charles Harrison. 1855 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence. 1853 (Box 16, Folder 191)
    See also: Bromley, Isaac Hill, box 3, folder 24.
  - Stedman, James. 1801 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Steel, Samuel. 1737 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - Steele, Elphalet. 1764
    See: Steel, Samuel, box 16, folder 191.
    See: Thomson, Charles Steele, box 17, folder 201.
  - Steele, Henry Thornton. 1846 (Box 16, Folder 192)
    See also: Steele, Nathaniel, box 16, folder 192.
  - Steele, Julius. 1811 (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - Steele, Marshfield. 1790 (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - Steele, Nathaniel. 1788 (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - Steele, Thomas Clark. 1863 (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - Steiner, Bernard Christian. 1888
    See: Stuart, Charles Augustus, box 17, folder 196.
  - Steiner, Lewis Henry. 1869h (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - Sterling, Elisha. 1787
    See: Sterling, John Montgomery, box 16, folder 192.
  - Sterling, John Montgomery. 1820 (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - Stevens, Alexander Hodgdon. 1807 (Box 16, Folder 193)
    See also: Stevens, John Austin, box 21, folder 255.
  - Stevens, Asahel Augustus. 1843 (Box 16, Folder 193)
  - Stevens, Byam Kerby. 1811 (Box 16, Folder 193)
  - Stevens, Frederic Morton. 1851 (Box 16, Folder 193)
  - Stevens, John Austin. 1813
    See: Stevens, John Austin, box 21, folder 255.
  - Stevens, Ledyard. 1864
    See: Stevens, Alexander Hodgdon, box 16, folder 193.
  - Stevens, Phineas. 1828m (Box 16, Folder 193)
  - Stevens, Samuel. 1805
  - Stewart, John Tweed. 1872 (Box 16, Folder 193)
  - Stiles, Ezra. 1746 (Box 16, Folder 193)
    See also: Series II, box 23, folder 5.
  - Stiles, Robert Augustus. 1859 (Box 16, Folder 193)
  - Stillé, Charles Janeway. 1839 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Stillson, William Bostwick. 1817 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Stocking, Sabin. 1855h (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Stoddard, John. 1787 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Stoddard, John Marshall Fayette. 1833 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Stoddard, William. 1804 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Stone, Aaron Ely. 1847l (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Stone, Charles Stewart. 1842 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Stone, Mason Albert. 1900
    See: Watson, John, box 18, folder 213.
  - Stone, Randolph. 1815 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Stone, Seth Bradley. 1842 (Box 16, Folder 194)
  - Storrs, Eleazar. 1762 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Storrs, Experience. 1759 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Storrs, Huckins. 1816m (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Storrs, Richard Salter. 1783m
    See: Williston, David Howe, box 19, folder 225.
  - Storrs, Richard Salter. 1865h (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Storrs, Zalmon. 1801 (Box 17, Folder 195)
    See also: Storrs, Experience, box 17, folder 195.
  - Street, Augustus Russell. 1812
    See:Wooster, Joseph Lucius, box 19, folder 232.
  - Street, Harlow Lowndes. 1826 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Street, Owen. 1837 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Adonijah. 1786
    See: Strong, William Lightbourn, box 17, folder 195.
  - Strong, Benjamin. 1734 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Charles Hamot. 1877
    See: Strong, Benjamin, box 17, folder 195.
  - Strong, Cyprian. 1763 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, David. 1745 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Edward Augustus. 1821 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Elisha Beebe. 1809 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Ephraim. 1792 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, George Arthur. 1871
  - Strong, Henry Adgate. 1873
  - Strong, John. 1766 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, John Calvin. 1842 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Joseph. 1749
    See: Strong, Theodore, box 17, folder 195.
    See: Strong, Woodbridge, box 17, folder 195.
  - Strong, Joseph. 1784
  - Strong, Josiah Bartlett. 1806 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Maltby. 1819
  - Strong, Nehemiah. 1755 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Nelson Hooker. 1876
  - Strong, Selah Brewster. 1811 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Theodore. 1812 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Theodore Chester. 1878
  - Strong, Theron Roundell. 1903
  - Strong, Thomas Barnard. 1800 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, Ullman. 1873
  - Strong, William Lightbourn. 1802 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Strong, William Thaddeus. 1876
  - Strong, Woodbridge. 1815 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Stuart, Charles Augustus. 1803 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Stuart, James Clark. 1831 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Stuart, Morgan. 1835m (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Stuart, Moses. 1799 (Box 17, Folder 196)
    See: Stuart, James Clark, box 17, folder 196.
  - Sturgeon, William. 1745 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Sturges, Charles Dimon. 1848 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Sturges, Jonathan. 1759
  - Sturtevant, Ephraim Tanner. 1826 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Sturtevant, Julian Monson. 1826 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Sullivan, Cornelius. 1869 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Sullivan, John Langdon. 1837m (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Sumner, Clement. 1758 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Sumner, William. 1749 non-graduate (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Sumner, William. 1761 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Surridge, Charles Granville. 1879m (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Sutherland, Jacob. 1807 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Sweet, Delevan Sumner. 1879 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Sweet, Edward. 1844 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Sweet, Preston Irving. 1858 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Swift, Charles Albert. 1856 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Swift, Earl. 1805 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Swift, Erastus. 1800 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Swift, Frederick Booth. 1852 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Swift, George. 1816 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Swift, Heman. 1797h (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Swift, Henry. 1804 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Swift, William Fitch. 1872l (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Swift, Zephaniah. 1778
    See: Swift, George, box 17, folder 197.
  - Taintor, Edwin Bulkeley. 1821 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Taintor, Giles. 1812 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Taintor, John Adam. 1821
    See: Taintor, Edwin Bulkeley, box 17, folder 197.
  - Talcott, Joel. 1824 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Talcott, Samuel. 1757
    See: Talcott, Thomas Grosvenor, box 17, folder 198.
  - Talcott, Thomas Grosvenor. 1838 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Tallmadge, Benjamin. 1830h
    See: box 21, folder 256.
  - Tallmadge, Frederick Augustus. 1811 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Tallmadge, John Smith. 1818 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Tallmadge, Leander Allen. 1855 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Tarbell, Grosvenor. 1794 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Tarbox, Luther Goulding. 1853 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Taylor, Charles Wiley. 1807 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Taylor, Daniel. 1707 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Taylor, Edward. 1817 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Taylor, Fitch Waterman. 1828 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Taylor, George. 1824m
  - Taylor, James. 1754 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel William. 1807
    See: Taylor, George, box 21, folder 256.
  - Taylor, Robert Eveleigh. 1854 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Taylor, William. 1787 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Taylor, William Augustine. 1803 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Ten Eyck, Henry. 1777 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Tennant, Charles Joseph. 1863m (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Tennent, Sidney. 1847 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Tenney, George Champlin. 1829 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Terry, Shadrach. 1819 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Thacher, George. 1840 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Thacher, Josiah. 1765h (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Thayer, Henry Wolcott. 1862 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Thayer, William Roscoe. 1915h (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Thomas, John. 1811 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Thomas, Landon Addison. 1822 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Thomas, Robert S. 1844h
  - Thompson, Alexander Baldwin. 1831 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thompson, Andrew. 1826 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thompson, Augustus Charles. 1841h (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thompson, Chauncey Minott. 1854 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thompson, Guy Van Gorder. 1894 Ph.D. (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thompson, James. 1789
  - Thompson, John Hansen. 1845m (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thompson, Thomas Merritt. 1844 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thomson, Asahel. 1810 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thomson, Charles Steele. 1822m (Box 17, Folder 201)
    See also: Thomson, Horatio, box 17, folder 201.
  - Thomson, Ernest Le Roy. 1874m
  - Thomson, Horatio. 1827m (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thomson, William Hanna. 1861h (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Thomson, William Henry. 1862m (Box 17, Folder 201)
    See also: Thomson, Charles Steele, box 17, folder 201.
  - Thornton, Joseph Lyle. 1887 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Thrall, George Sanford. 1877 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Throckmorton, Samuel Reading. 1863 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Throop, Benjamin. 1734
    See: Dyer, Jabez, box 6, folder 58.
  - Tiffany, William Henry. 1840 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Tillotson, George Jeffrey. 1825 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Tingley, Pelatiah. 1761 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Tinker, Anson Phelps. 1868 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Titus, William Ustick. 1817 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Tod, George. 1795
  - Todd, Albert. 1836 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Todd, George Thompson. 1829 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Todd, Jonathan. 1732 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Todd, Samuel. 1734
  - Todd, Walker. 1810 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Tomlinson, Daniel. 1781 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Tomlinson, Gideon. 1802 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Tomlinson, John Atwood. 1856h
    See:box 21, folder 256.
  - Toplift, Jerome. 1756 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Toplift, Stephen. 1825 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Topping, Josiah. 1749 (Box 17, Folder 203)
    See also: Smith, Richard (1797), box 16, folder 187.
    See also: Young, David, box 19, folder 234.
  - Torrey, Charles Turner. 1833 (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Tousey, Thomas. 1707 (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Townsend, Daniel Jenkins. 1828 (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Townsend, George Pollok Devereux. 1886p (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Townsend, Platt. 1750 (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Townsend, William. 1773 (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Tracy, Fanning. 1796 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Tracy, Phineas Lyman. 1806 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Train, Elijah Nickerson. 1827 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Trapier, William Heyward. 1824 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Trask, Charles Hooker. 1846 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Trask, John Boardman. 1859h (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Treadway, James. 1759 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Treat, Charles. 1722
    See: box 21, folder 257.
  - Treat, Richard. 1719 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Treat, Richard. 1725 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Treat, Samuel. 1734 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Tredwell, Timothy. 1875h (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Trotter, Silas Flournoy. 1839 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trow, George William. 1858h (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trowbridge, Daniel. 1725 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trowbridge, Joseph. 1763 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trowbridge, William Henry. 1855m (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trumbull, Benjamin. 1759 (Box 17, Folder 205)
    See also: Jones, Isaac (1792), box 21, folder 247.
    See also: Newell, Abel, box 21, folder 251.
    See also: Perry, Joshua, box 21, folder 252.
    See also: Sherman, Josiah, box 21, folder 254.
    See also: Tullar, Martin, box 21, folder 257.
  - Trumbull, Charles Edward. 1854 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trumbull, David. 1842
    See: Trumbull, Stephen, box 17, folder 205.
  - Trumbull, James Hammond. 1842 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trumbull, James Heddon. 1848 (Box 17, Folder 205)
    See also: Trumbull, Ricardo Lindsay, box 17, folder 205.
  - Trumbull, John. 1767 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trumbull, John. 1878
  - Trumbull, John Heyward. 1881p
    See: Trumbull, Ricardo Lindsay, box 17, folder 205.
  - Trumbull, Jonathan George Washington. 1807 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trumbull, Ricardo Lindsay. 1881p (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trumbull, Stephen. 1880 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Trumbull, William. 1883
  - Tucker, James Wakefield. 1807 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Tucker, John Harvey. 1796 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Tudor, Samuel. 1728 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Tullar, David. 1774 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Tullar, Martin. 1777
  - Turner, Asa. 1827 (Box 17, Folder 206)
    See also: Turner, Henry Holmes, box 17, folder 206.
  - Turner, Edward. 1818 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Turner, Henry Holmes. 1858 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Turner, Thomas. 1815 (Box 17, Folder 206)
    See also: Spruill, George Evans, box 16, folder 190.
  - Tuthill, Samuel. 1745 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Tuttle, John Todd. 1830m (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tuttle, Moses. 1745
  - Tuttle, Oswin Hinckley. 1879l (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tuttle, Timothy. 1808 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tweedy, Edwin Augustus. 1831m (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tweedy, John Hubbard. 1834 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Twining, Alexander Catlin. 1820 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Twining, Theodore Woolsey. 1858 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tyler, Bennett. 1804 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tyler, Charles Mellen. 1855 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tyler, Daniel Putnam. 1830h (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tyler, David Atwater. 1844m (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tyler, Edwin. 1848 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tyler, John. 1765 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tyler, Lemuel. 1780 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tyler, Septimius. 1808 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Tytus, Edward Jefferson. 1868 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Udall, Richard Athil. 1830 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Ufford, Edward Goodrich. 1845m (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Ufford, Hezekiah Gold. 1806 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Upham, George Leland. 1875p (Box 17, Folder 208)
    See also: Upham, William Richard, box 17, folder 208.
  - Upham, Nathan. 1853 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Upham, William Richard. 1874p (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Vaill, Herman Landon. 1824h
  - Van Allen, John. 1834m (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Van Benthuysen, Jacob. 1815 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Van Bergen, Peter Anthony. 1832 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Van Buren, William Holme. 1838 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Vanderbilt, Jeremiah. 1804 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Vanderburgh, Federal. 1826m
  - Van Deursen, William. 1801 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Van Heuvel, Jacob Adrien. 1804 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Van Horne, John. 1749 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Van Huyk, Albert Leverett. 1893p (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Van Matre, Daniel. 1820 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Van Rensselaer, Jeremiah. 1813 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Van Vleck, Charles Williams. 1876 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Van Vleck, William. 1876 non-graduate (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Varnum, James Mitchell. 1868 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Varnum, Joseph Bradley. 1838 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Vaughan, Henry. 1818 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Vaughan, John A. 1822 non-graduate (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Vermilye, Thomas Edward. 1822 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Ver Planck, William Gordon. 1823 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Vincent, Frank. 1870 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Vining, Edward Payson. 1886h (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Vose, George Franklin. 1859 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Wadhams, Noah. 1764h
    See: Wadhams, Solomon, box 18, folder 210.
  - Wadhams, Solomon. 1762 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Wadsworth, Adrian Rowe. 1837 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Wadsworth, James. 1841 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Wadsworth, Strong. 1851 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Wagner, [John]. [1812] (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Waite, Calvin. 1816h (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Waite, Ezra. 1782 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Waite, George Chapman. 1840 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Waite, Henry Matson. 1809
    See: Waite, Ezra, box 18, folder 210.
    See: Waite, George Chapman, box 18, folder 210.
  - Waite, Morisson Remick. 1837
  - Waite, Richard. 1853
  - Wakefield, John Luman. 1847m (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Wakefield, Leander Elmer. 1842 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Wakeman, Ebenezer. 1720
  - Wakeman, Stephen. 1738 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Walbridge, Ames. 1826m (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Walcott, John Alexander. 1828m (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Waldo, Joseph T. 1819m (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Wales, Eleazar. 1753 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Wales, Isaac Miles. 1793 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Wales, John. 1801 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Wales, Leonard Eugene. 1807
  - Wales, Samuel. 1767
    See: Wales, Isaac Miles, box 18, folder 211.
  - Walker, Edward. 1757h (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Walker, Joseph Knox. 1838 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Walker, Robert. 1730 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Walker, Willis Ephraim. 1871 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Walkley, James Clark. 1836 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Wallace, Thomas Smith. 1848 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Wallis, John Spencer. 1832 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Waln, Edward. 1831 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Waln, Samuel Morris. 1877 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Walsh, Hugh. 1835 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Walton, John. 1720
  - Ward, Isaac Moreau. 1825 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Ward, Samuel Dexter. 1809 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Wardwell, Daniel Wardwell. 1872p (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Waring, Charles Bill. 1849 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Waring, Samuel Copp. 1847 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Warner, Edward. 1835 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Warner, Egbert Randal. 1876m (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Warner, Ely. 1807 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Warner, Isaac Welton. 1832 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Warner, Jared Clark. 1854
    See: Warner, Ely, box 18, folder 212.
  - Warner, John Carrington. 1804 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Warner, Noadiah. 1759 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Warner, Richard. 1817 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Washington, George. 1839
  - Waterbury, Jared Bell. 1822 (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Waterman, Elijah. 1791 (Box 18, Folder 213)
    See also: Waterman, Thomas Glasby (1806), box 18, folder 213.
  - Waterman, Joshua Whitney. 1844 (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Waterman, Sigismond. 1848m (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Waterman, Simon. 1759 (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Waterman, Thomas Glasby. 1806 (Box 18, Folder 213)
    See also: Chamberlain, Robert Linton, box 4, folder 34.
  - Waterman, Thomas Glasby. 1886 (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Waters, Francis. 1822h (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Watkins, Claibourne A. 1834h (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Watkins, Hezekiah. 1859
    See: box 21, folder 258.
  - Watrous, John Richard. 1818h
    See: Watrous, John Richard (1848), box 18, folder 213.
  - Watrous, John Richard. 1848 (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Watson, James Tyler. 1776 (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Watson, John. 1764 (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Way, Francis Roscoe. 1860
  - Weaver, Daniel B. 1882 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Webb, Nathaniel. 1757 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Weber, John Charles. 1874p (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Webster, Charles. 1863 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Webster, Elisha. 1738 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Webster, Ira. 1802 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Webster, Noah. 1778
    See: Steele, Henry Thornton, box 16, folder 192.
  - Webster, Pelatiah. 1746
    See:box 21, folder 258.
  - Weed, John William. 1813 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Weiser, Erastus Hay. 1849 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Welch, Archibald. 1836h
  - Welch, Daniel. 1749 (Box 18, Folder 214)
    See also: Welch, Jonathan Ashley, box 18, folder 214.
  - Welch, Harmanus Madison. 1875 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Welch, Jonathan Ashley. 1813 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Welch, Moses Cooke. 1792
  - Welch, William Wickham. 1839m (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Weld, Lewis. 1818
    See: Weld, Lewis Ledyard, box 18, folder 215.
  - Weld, Lewis Ledyard. 1854 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, Charles Roger. 1834 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, Elijah Gardiner. 1808h (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, Thomas Norton. 1830 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, Gaylord. 1809 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, George. 1779 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, Gideon. 1753 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, Martin. 1806 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, Roger. 1775
  - Welles, Samuel. 1707 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, Solomon. 1739
  - Welles, Thomas. 1774 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Welles, William. 1779 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Wellington, Asa. 1843 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Wells, Eben Hale. 1881 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Wells, Edmund. 1768 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Wells, Horatio Thomas. 1853h (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Wells, John Freme. 1844m (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Wells, Nathaniel. 1829 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Wells, Ralph. 1810 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Wells, Sylvester. 1781 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Welton, Willard. 1806 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Wesson, Charles Howland. 1863 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Wesson, Lorenzo. 1846 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - West, Jeremiah. 1774 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - West, Nathaniel. 1768 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Westervelt, Tompkins. 1850l (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Weston, Hervey Eliphaz. 1839 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Wetmore, Charles Henry. 1804 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wetmore, Izrahiah, 1748
    See: Wetmore, Charles Henry, box 18, folder 217.
  - Wetmore, James. 1714 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wetmore, Noah. 1757 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wheaton, Nathaniel Sheldon. 1814 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wheeler, Arthur Martin. 1857 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wheeler, Charles Mortimer. 1859 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wheeler, Fitch. 1820 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wheeler, Hiram. 1833 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wheeler, William. 1779 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wheeler, William. 1855 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wheelock, Eleazar. 1733 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Wheelock, Ralph. 1765
  - Whelpley, William Avery, (1807) (Box 18, Folder 217)
    See also: Raymond, Dvaid Hillhouse, box 14, folder 164.
  - White, Addison Hayes. 1823 (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - White, Andrew Judson. 1846m (Box 18, Folder 218)
    See also: Erving, Joel Fuller, box 7, folder 63.
  - White Charles Atwood. 1854
  - White, Charles Coomer. 1783 (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - White, Chester. 1825 (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - White, Clement Brooke. 1872 (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - White, Ebenezer. 1733
  - White, Ebenezer Russell. 1760
  - White, Frederick. 1815 (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - White, George Edward. 1866
  - White, Henry. 1821
  - White, Henry Dyer. 1851
  - White, John. 1774
  - White, Joseph. 1868h (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - White, Oliver Sherman. 1864